shop4reebok.com 2011-05-15

# Privacy Policy - Reebok

Reebok International Limited ("Reebok") respects the privacy of visitors to the Reebok websites. Reebok has adopted this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to inform you of what information we collect from you on or through the websites located at the following domain names: www.reebok.com, www.rbk.com and www.rbkcustom.com (collectively, the "Websites"), how we collect that information, how we may use it and the steps we take to protect it.

This Privacy Policy applies only to these Websites. Reebok is not responsible for the privacy practices of any company to which our Websites might link. For access to the privacy policies of those sites, please refer to the policies provided by those sites at their home pages.

**Your Consent**

Reebok will not collect personal information from you without your express consent. By clicking the "I agree" button at the end of this privacy policy, you signify that you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, which governs the collection and use of personal information via the Websites, as well as to our Terms and Conditions.

**What kind of information do we collect?**

**Personal Information**

Reebok collects personal information when you open an account, submit orders or purchase merchandise from the Website, or otherwise provide information to participate in the services and offerings on the Website. On such occasions, the personal information collected by or on behalf of Reebok may include, without limitation: your name, e-mail address, date of birth, billing address, shipping address, postcode, telephone number, mobile phone number, credit card information, debit card and related information, information concerning your interests, and other demographic information, as applicable. We may also ask some additional optional questions to help us better serve you. Please note that when you make a purchase from any of the Websites, we may need to contact you via phone, postal mail or e-mail if we have questions regarding your order.

To customise our response to your preferences with your consent, Reebok may ask you for personal information, such as your name, address, date of birth, gender, e-mail address, telephone number, mobile phone number and similar information. We do this, for instance, when you establish a user profile or account, register for contests and promotions, submit requests to Reebok customer service, respond to communications from Reebok and for other services that require registration or subscription. When you establish a user profile, we may also request optional information from you regarding certain user preferences and similar information. In addition, personal information is collected in certain portions of the Websites in which visitors specifically and knowingly provide such information along with content submissions, community postings (e.g., chat or bulletin boards), suggestions, surveys, polls or voting.

Reebok may also collect personal information from you about a third party to carry out services relating to you or that third party at your request. For instance, you may provide us with personal information about a third party when you request that we ship an order to a third party or to send an e-mail or e-postcard to a third party. That information will only be used for the specific purpose of responding to your request, such as delivering the e-postcard or to process and ship the order and confirm shipment.

**Non-Personal and Aggregate Data**

When you visit our Websites, we may collect "click stream" data (IP address, server address, domain name, browser information, and other non-personally identifiable information regarding your visit. This information may be combined with information you have provided to us (for instance by registering), which will enable us to analyse and better customise your visits. Like many websites, we may collect information regarding website usage by using cookies and tracking technologies. We may use information gathered from the cookies and tracking technologies to analyse and understand how the Websites are used and to enhance your visits to the Websites. For example, we may use cookies and tracking technologies to: (i) customise account pages for you; (ii) track user visits and account set-ups; (iii) determine what set-ups are most frequently requested; and (iv) provide for a "remember me" function to save your user name and password so you do not have to provide it each time you visit the Websites. You can find more information on how we use cookies in the section titled "Use of Cookies".

We may also use a third-party service provider to help us optimise the products and services we offer through the Websites. That third party may place web beacons or data tags on the Websites and/or a cookie on your computer to facilitate collection of information on use of the Websites each time you visit the Website ("Session Data"). If, at any time you do not wish to allow your Session Data to be aggregated and analysed by that third party, you may visit the following web page and utilise the opt-out mechanism found there. This opt-out mechanism is only applicable to cookies placed on your computer by that third party.

**Use of Cookies**

A "cookie" is a small string of information that the website that you visit transfers to your computer for identification purposes. Cookies can be used to follow your activity on the Websites and that information helps us to understand your preferences and improve your website experience. Cookies are also used to remember user information such as your user name and password.

You can turn off all cookies if you prefer not to receive them. You can also have your computer warn you whenever cookies are being used. For both options you must adjust your browser settings. Please note than when you set your computer to reject cookies, the settings may limit the functionality of the website you visit and it is possible that you will not have access to some of the features on the website.

**Use of Visitors' Information**

Except for the purposes set forth below and otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, Reebok will not share, sell, trade or otherwise transfer personal information provided by you on or through the Websites to third parties without informing you in advance. We will primarily use your personal information to provide products and services to you and to perform the following:

_Business Uses_ \- Reebok uses the personal information that you provide to: (i) establish user profiles and accounts and store user preferences; (ii) administer and fulfil contests, promotions, surveys or other site features (for instance to deliver a prize you may have won in a contest); (iii) provide you with the products or services that you have ordered or requested; (iv) process and ship orders; (v) send order and shipping confirmations; (vi) provide customer service; (vii) process returns or exchanges; and (viii) protect you, and us, against error and fraud; (ix) keep records of returns and exchanges; and (x) as needed to investigate or enforce legal rights and obligations:

In addition, if you have opted-in to receive communications, including e-mails and/or SMS messages from Reebok we will use personal information provided by you to customise advertising and content we present to you, and to send you information and materials, including, without limitation, via e-mail or SMS messages about products, offers and news we think could interest you. This information may relate to products, offers and news of Reebok or its licensees or carefully selected commercial partners.

_Third-Parties_ \- Information collected on or through the Websites may be shared or transferred to third parties who may be located outside the United Kingdom who perform services for us or with whom we contract for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may use third parties to host our Websites, assist in designing and operating the Websites or certain features, perform services (e.g., prize fulfilment), print or send communications on behalf of Reebok, authorise and process payments, process and administer gift cards, provide customer service and help us analyse data.

Reebok requires that these third-party providers to employ a comparable level of protection for personal consumer information. Further, Reebok only provides these third-party providers with the personal information necessary to perform their designated functions and services for us. You may be asked on certain areas our Websites whether you wish to receive information from third parties and, upon your consent, Reebok and/or those third parties may use the personal information you provide to contact you consistent with the consent that you provided as permitted by applicable law.

_Affiliated Businesses; Business Transfers_ \- We may share the personal information you have provided us among our affiliated businesses that we control or that are under common control with us. They may use this information to offer products and services to you consistent with the purposes identified in this Privacy Policy, to the extent permitted by applicable law. The personal information that we collect may also be transferred as an asset in connection with a merger or sale (including any transfers made as a part of an insolvency or bankruptcy proceeding) involving all or part of Reebok or as part of a corporate reorganisation, stock sale or change of control.

_Required Disclosures_ \- We may share personal information you provide to us with a third party if we are required by law to disclose that personal information. For example, we may be required to disclose personal information to respond to a subpoena, court order or other legal process, including any administrative proceeding, or in connection with an investigation. We may also disclose this information in response to a law enforcement agency's request or as otherwise required or permitted by law when the information is relevant to investigating a violation of law or to address an emergency that threatens an individual's life, health or security.

_Non-Personal Information_ \- We may use non-personal information to analyse visits to the Websites and learn about the interests of our visitors in aggregate and to better understand your interests and needs, so we can improve our products and services and deliver to you the type of content, features and promotions in which you are most interested. We may share non-personal, aggregate data with our marketing partners or other third parties for research and marketing purposes.

We may on occasion combine information we received on or through the Websites with information obtained from other sources and outside records to enable us to update and correct the information contained in our database.

**Who Manages Visitors' Information**

The global and local websites of Reebok and the information collected, are managed and controlled by Reebok or by third- party service providers that are required to maintain the security and confidentiality standards described in this Privacy Policy on behalf of Reebok. The servers that make the Websites available and that store the information collected by Reebok are located in the United Kingdom.

**Protection of Visitors' Information**

Reebok takes administrative, technical and physical precautions to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorised access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction and requires its third-party service providers to do the same.

You can help us by also taking precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet by changing your passwords often, using a combination of letters and numbers, and making sure you use a secure web browser.

**Children's Privacy**

For the United States, Canada, Australia, and the European Union only, Reebok does not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 for marketing purposes, because some information is collected electronically, it can appear to be the personal information of the Reebok purchaser of the product, and will be treated as such by this privacy policy. If a child under 13 submits personal information to Reebok and we learn that that personal information is the information of a child under 13, we will attempt to delete the information as soon as possible.

For Brazil only, Reebok does not knowing collect personal information from children under 16. If a child under age 16 submits personal information to Reebok and we learn that the personal information is the information of a child under 16, we will attempt to delete that information as soon as possible.

Except as stated above for the specific countries identified, Reebok does not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18 and in a country that prohibits the collection of personal data from persons under the age of 18, you should not provide any personal information to us and you should use the Websites only with the involvement or a parent or guardian.

**Right of Access**

You have a right to access your personal information. You may exercise this right by visiting the "My Account" section of the website. From this link, you can view, challenge, modify or delete your personal information from our database. Please note that Reebok reserves the right to retain personal information relating to you reasonably necessary to document its business activities or as needed for required disclosures.

**Choices You Have**

No one is required to provide us with personal information. Your provision of any personal information to us on or through our Websites or by other means must be voluntary and with your consent to the uses described in this Privacy Policy. In some cases, only persons who provide the requested personal information will be able to order products and services or otherwise participate in the Websites' activities and offerings.

If you would like to be on our e-mail list, you will be provided with the opportunity to designate your preference on the Website. You will also have the opportunity to "opt-in" to join our mailing list to receive catalogues and related materials through the mail. In addition, if you provide your mobile phone number and would like to receive text messages and/or SMS messages from us, you will have the opportunity to "opt-in" to receive those communications.

**Opt-Outs**

If you want to opt-out of having your personal information shared with our affiliates please visit the "My Account" section of the Websites, or send a letter to Reebok at: 

Reebok International Headquarters 

Digital Marketing Department 

1895 JW Foster Blvd 

Canton, MA 02021 

You also will have the opportunity to opt-out of receiving future e-mail communications by clicking on an "unsubscribe" hyperlink contained in promotional, commercial e-mails we send to you.

Please note that unless you cancel your registration, you will not be able to opt-out of receiving all types of communications, such as service announcements and administrative messages, as these types of communications are a necessary part of your account and use of the Websites.

**Cancellation of Registration**

You may cancel your user registration at any time, and you can choose to opt-out of receiving any future e-mails and/or SMS messages from Reebok. Please note that modifications of the status of personal information will not stop e-mails and/or SMS messages (i) generated before Reebok can accomplish the modification of the status of personal information or (ii) from third parties with whom Reebok my have already shared that personal information consistent with this Privacy Policy.

**Changes to the Policy**

Reebok may update its privacy policy from time to time due to changes in regulations and to keep up with new developments and possibilities on the internet. When we change the policy in a material way a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated privacy policy.

**How you can contact us**

If you have questions, comments, a problem exercising your rights to access and correct information, or want to register a compliant relating to our website and/or privacy policy, please write to us at:

Reebok International 

Attn: Digital Marketing 

1895 J.W Foster Blvd. 

Canton, MA 02021

Last Updated 31 March 2008
